{
    "homeworks": [
        {
            "id": "3d3a0a7e-6d92-4998-992d-4f77dc7f8315",
            "name": "Homework 2021/04/28",
            "__class": "Homework",
            "__ver": "1",
            "status": "new",
            "tasks": [
                {
                    "id": "21fd2a98-8707-42db-8d65-b3ca95725573",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "correctAnswer": 5,
                    "problem": "2 + 3"
                },
                {
                    "id": "528dc7a5-7328-446c-bafb-8004833968d0",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "correctAnswer": 9,
                    "problem": "6 + 3"
                },
                {
                    "id": "92a997e5-bcd2-4308-b682-adf138cd67f2",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "correctAnswer": 14,
                    "problem": "6 + 8"
                },
                {
                    "id": "9c8b2b5a-f901-48c1-8194-bc6bb0ea0c9b",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "correctAnswer": 8,
                    "problem": "6 + 2"
                },
                {
                    "id": "964e37d4-1b6d-4bd9-b0a4-3908d6831c19",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "correctAnswer": 6,
                    "problem": "3 + 3"
                },
                {
                    "id": "46d5cf55-5073-4d52-b44c-e24b075dbcc2",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "correctAnswer": 3,
                    "problem": "8 - 5"
                },
                {
                    "id": "fa434c0c-4a81-439e-b721-e70d1a978357",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "correctAnswer": 3,
                    "problem": "9 - 6"
                },
                {
                    "id": "2e4ceba2-1da4-4768-bb2e-48e3ca4e341d",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "AudioMatchTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "expected": 27
                },
                {
                    "id": "320d9a43-febf-4f53-a67f-bc86413d75bd",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "AudioMatchTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "expected": 13
                },
                {
                    "id": "8438408c-cfb6-4497-a8b7-3a54944849fa",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "AudioMatchTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "expected": 42
                },
                {
                    "id": "d082c5ff-cf4a-4fdf-a887-f0c839958888",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "AudioMatchTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "expected": 35
                },
                {
                    "id": "8083b20e-2d2f-42f0-9def-fabc5b04e8db",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "AudioMatchTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "expected": 14
                },
                {
                    "id": "92c5c32f-f3f8-4e23-bae0-fa8c77957128",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "correctAnswer": 13,
                    "problem": "10 + 3"
                },
                {
                    "id": "f50b9a6f-646a-4804-8c54-edec1ec2e216",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "correctAnswer": 39,
                    "problem": "30 + 9"
                },
                {
                    "id": "afd7ca5c-4106-450f-a52e-8c72bffce208",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "correctAnswer": 23,
                    "problem": "20 + 3"
                },
                {
                    "id": "f9f77f78-a5b7-436c-b796-a366ba14daea",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "correctAnswer": 38,
                    "problem": "30 + 8"
                },
                {
                    "id": "6801e524-06ce-4922-9875-b6d45f3ca611",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "2",
                    "correctAnswer": 17,
                    "problem": "10 + 7"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}